teenhollywood.com 2001-12-01

# TEENHOLLYWOOD.COM - Privacy Policy

|    
  
A member of the [](http://www.totalwoman.com/)  
Network  
|    
|   
---  
**TeenVillage Network Privacy Statement**  
 **Privacy Statement**  
Your privacy is important to us. In order to protect your privacy, we have put together a privacy statement so that you are aware of our data collection activities. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, please contact TeenHollywood.com, Inc. 444 5th Ave SW, Suite 1805 Calgary, AB T2P 2T8 Canada or e-mail us at [info@teenhollywood.com](mailto:info@teenhollywood.com).  
 **Children Under 13**  
Our web sites are not directed to children under the age of 13, and as such we do not allow the registration by children under the age of 13. TeenHollywood.com, Inc. does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from kids under 13.  
 **Parents**  
You may specifically request to review or delete your child’s information from our database by e-mailing [info@teenhollywood.com](mailto:info@teenhollywood.com). If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please e-mail [info@teenhollywood.com](mailto:info@teenhollywood.com).  
 **Information Collection and Use**  
Our web sites collect information required to participate in certain activities through our web site. "Cookies," initially containing no personally identifiable information, are used to track user “sessions”. If you sign up for a member account, personally identifiable information may be included in the cookies sent by our servers and also stored in our database. “Personally identifiable information” includes your name, address, e-mail, phone number and any other information that can be used to tell another person who you are. Our sites may use order forms and/or registration forms for signing up for an account, ordering a product or requesting further information. Information collected includes contact information (i.e. e-mail address, name, address and phone number) and financial information (credit card information). Contact information collected is used to send order confirmations, orders, statistical tracking and to send information about our products and services. Contact information may also be used by 3rd party advertisers as described below. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings and are given the opportunity to do so each time they register or order on-line. 3rd party advertisers who wish to provide you with product or service information may have their messages distributed to our member list, at which point users are able to opt-out of future mailings. **WE DO NOT RE-SELL OR DISTRIBUTE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANY 3RD PARTIES**. We do not require our members to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in activities on our sites.  
 **Cookies**  
Cookies are used to track information including personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser to reject or prompt before receiving cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, this may impair your ability to use our sites and it will require you to re-sign-in each time that you visit our sites. 3rd Party advertisers may also use cookies on our site. Our privacy policy does not cover 3rd party advertiser use of cookies on our site as we have no control over their use of data.  
 **Polls and Surveys**  
When you participate in polls or surveys on our sites, your anonymity is maintained at all times. If survey results are provided to outside parties, all personally identifiable information is removed and data is reported only in aggregate.  
 **Aggregate and Summary Information**  
TeenHollywood.com, Inc. may share non-personal, summary information regarding our users with 3rd parties. This information is not personally identifiable information.  
 **Promotions, Sweepstakes and Contests**  
We may ask you for personally identifiable information when you enter sweepstakes, contests, or other events requiring the awarding (i.e. mailing) of prizes. If you do not wish to have this data collected, please do not participate in these contests.  
 **Newsletters**  
Our newsletters are generally sent out on a weekly basis, plus occasional “special editions” featuring special events or advertisers. We do not disclose our newsletter subscriber list to any third parties except as required for the delivery of the newsletter. Each newsletter sent includes an "unsubscribe" option if you do not wish to receive future mailings.  
 **Disclosure to Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose user information to government authorities as required by law or as deemed necessary. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  
 **Sale of Assets**  
In the event that TeenHollywood.com, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.  
 **Interactive Services**  
Interactive services on our site include chat rooms, profiles and message boards. Users must be 13 or older to use or register for these services. TeenHollywood.com, Inc. reserves the right to monitor our interactive services, but does not warrant that it will be able to do so at all times. **PERSONAL INFORMATION SUCH AS FULL NAME, SCHOOL, ADDRESS OR PHONE NUMBER SHOULD NEVER BE POSTED IN OUR INTERACTIVE SERVICES. FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY, DO NOT POST SUCH INFORMATION.**  
 **Linked Sites**  
There are many opportunities throughout our sites to "link" to other web sites that are beyond our control. These sites, including sites owned by our advertisers, usually do not follow our privacy policies and as a result we are not responsible for your activities on other sites or the use of your personally identifiable information by other sites.  
 **3rd Party Advertisements/Ad Serving**  
Third party ad servers and agencies serve ads to our web sites. They may collect information about surfing behaviors and user interests. For specific information regarding their privacy policies, view [Doubleclick's](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy) and [Engage's](http://www.engage.com/privacy/) privacy policies. Information shared with third party advertisers for the purposes of ad serving is not personally identifiable. Information collected from users' visits to this site and other sites may be used by some third party advertisers to determine which ads to serve to the user on this site and other sites. DoubleClick uses information about your visit to this site, such as the number of times that you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information) to serve ads to you only on this site. To opt out of receiving intelligent advertising targeting from third party advertisers, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).  
 **Security**  
TeenHollywood.com, Inc. maintains reasonable procedures to protect the confidentiality of our members information. Our servers are physically secure and are protected by firewall(s).  
 **Revision of Privacy Statement**  
We reserve the right to update this policy at any time. Material changes in our use of information (i.e. distribution of information to 3rd parties) will not take effect until a reasonable effort has been make to contact members via e-mail and a one week "opt-out" period has passed.   
|
